libertywritersnews.com 2017-02-21

# Privacy Policy * LIBERTY WRITERS NEWS

**PRIVACY POLICY NAVIGATION**

**II. Persons Under the Age of 13.**

**III. Information We Collect About You; How We Collect It.**

**IV. Third-Party Use of Cookies; Other Tracking Technologies.**

**V. How We Use Your Information.**

**VI. Disclosure of Your Information.**

**VII. Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information.**

**VIII. Accessing and Correcting Your Information.**

**IX. Deactivation; Termination of Your Account.**

**X. Your California Privacy Rights.**

**XI. Data Security.**

**XII. Communicating with You.**

**XIII. Changes to Our Privacy Policy.**

**XIV. Linking to the Website and Social Media Features.**

**XV. Links from the Website.**

**XVI. Geographic Restrictions.**

**XVII. Disclaimer of Warranties.**

**XVIII. Limitation on Liability.**

**XIX. Indemnification.**

**XX. Governing Law and Jurisdiction.**

**XXI. Dispute Resolution.**

**XXII. Limitation on Time to File Claims.**

**XXIII. Waiver; Severability.**

**XXIV. Entire Agreement.**

**XXV. Your Comments and Concerns.**

Last modified: December 7, 2016  

## **I. Introduction.**

**(A)** Liberty Writers News (“Company” or “We”) respects your privacy and is committed to protecting it through our compliance with this Privacy Policy (the “Privacy Policy”, as may be referred to in other Company documentation, including the Terms of Use). This policy describes (i) the types of information we may collect from you or that you may provide when you visit the website at, or utilize our Services (defined in the Website Terms of Use) from, www.libertywritersnews.com and all subdomains related thereto (our “Website”), and (ii) and our practices for collecting, using, maintaining, protecting, and disclosing that information.  
**(B)** This policy applies to information we collect:  
(i) on this Website;  
(ii) in email and other electronic messages between you and this Website; or  
(iii) when you interact with our advertising and applications on third-party websites and services, if those applications or advertising include links to this Privacy Policy.  
**(C)** It does not apply to information:  
(i) collected by us offline or through any other means, including on any other website operated by Company or any third party; or  
(ii) collected by any third party, including through any application or content (including advertising) that may link to or be accessible from or on the Website.  
**(D)** Please read this policy carefully to understand our policies and practices regarding your information and how we will treat it. If you do not agree with our policies and practices, your remedy is to not access or use our Website. This policy may change from time to time. Your continued use of this Website after we make changes is deemed to be acceptance of those changes, so please check the policy periodically for updates.  
**II. Persons Under the Age of 13.**  
Our Website is not intended for persons under 13 years of age. No one under age 13 may provide any personal information to or on the Website. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If you are under 13, you may not use the Services or register on the Website, make any purchases through the Website, use any of the interactive features of this Website or provide any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, email address, or any screen name or username you may use for your User Uploads (as defined in the Website Terms of Use). If we learn we have collected or received personal information from a person under 13, we will delete that information. If you believe (a) we might have any information from or about a child (under the age of 13, for these purposes), or (b) a user’s activities are inappropriate, please screenshot or save the offending user’s profile on the Website, where available, and email any additional supporting information you have to contact@libertywritersnews.com.  
**III. Information We Collect About You; How We Collect It.**  
**(A)** We collect several types of information from and about users of our Website, including information:  
(i) provided by you; to register for our newsletter, you will be asked for your full name and email address. In doing so, you authorize us to access certain account information related to the newsletter, such as your email address and any other information you provide (“personal information”). Further, you may be asked to allow the Website to collect your location information from your device when you use our Services or the Website, including identifying information, such as your name, address, email address and telephone number, and, if you transact business with us, some financial information. If you chat with other Website users or our user support team using any of our Services, you provide us the content of written chat transcripts. We may share or disclose your non-private, aggregated or otherwise non-personal information with third parties for industry analysis and demographic profiling and to deliver targeted advertising about other products and services and for marketing purposes. You may opt out of receiving marketing messages by using the opt-out mechanisms and links provided in each email;  
(ii) that is about you but individually does not identify you; or  
(iii) about your internet connection, the equipment you use to access our Website, and usage details.  
**(B)** We collect this information:  
(i) directly from you when you provide it to us;  
(ii) automatically as you navigate through the site. Information collected automatically may include usage details, IP addresses, and information collected through cookies and other tracking technologies; and  
(iii) automatically from your mobile device (including, without limitation, any mobile devices or tablets) when you use our Services, including your IP address, device ID and type, operating system, MAC address, browser type and language, the operating system, access times, geographic location while the application is actively running, and any referring website address.  
**(C)** The Website may allow access to or make available opportunities for you to view certain content and receive other products, services or other materials provided by us or third parties based on your location. To make these opportunities available to you, the Website may determine your location using one or more reference points, such as GPS, Bluetooth or software within your mobile device. If you have set your mobile device to disable GPS, Bluetooth or other location determining software, or do not authorize the Website to access your location data, you will not be able to access such location-specific content, products, services and materials. In addition, the Website may not function as intended by the Company.  
**(D)** The information we collect on or through our Website may include:  
(i) information that you provide by filling in forms on our Website. This includes information provided at the time of registering for our newsletter or contributing content in the form of User Uploads, subject to the Website Terms of Use. We may also ask you for information when you report a problem with our Services;  
(ii) records and copies of your correspondence (including email addresses), if you contact us; or  
(iii) your responses to surveys that we might ask you to complete for research purposes.  
As you navigate through and interact with our Services through the Website, we may use automatic data collection technologies to collect certain information about your equipment, browsing actions, and patterns, including details of your visits to the Website and use of our Services, including traffic data, location data, and other communication data and the resources that you access and use for our Services.  
**(E)** The information we collect automatically is statistical data, but we may maintain it or associate it with personal information we collect in other ways. It helps us to improve our Website, and to deliver a better and more personalized service, including by enabling us to:  
(i) estimate our audience size and usage patterns;  
(ii) store information about your preferences, allowing us to customize our Services according to your individual interests;  
(iii) speed up your searches and overall application infrastructure; or  
(iv) recognize you when you return to the Website, or use our Services.  
(F) The technologies we use for this automatic data collection may include:  
(i) Cookies (or browser cookies). A cookie is a small file placed on the hard drive of your computer or mobile device. You may refuse to accept browser cookies by activating the appropriate setting on your browser. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of our Website. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you direct your browser to our Website.  
(ii) Flash Cookies. Certain features of our Website may use local stored objects (or Flash cookies) to collect and store information about your preferences and navigation to, from, and on our Website. Flash cookies are not managed by the same browser settings as are used for browser cookies.  
(iii) Web Beacons; Pixel Tags. Pages of the Website may contain small electronic files known as web beacons (also referred to as clear gifs, pixel tags, and single-pixel gifs) that permit the Company, for example, to count users who have visited those pages or for other related website statistics (for example, recording the popularity of certain website content and verifying system and server integrity). Ad companies also use pixel tags to measure the number of ads displayed and their performance (such as how many people clicked on an ad).  
**IV. Third-Party Use of Cookies; Other Tracking Technologies.**  
**(A)** Some content or applications, including advertisements on the Website, are served by third-parties, including advertisers, ad networks and servers, content providers, and application providers. These third parties may use cookies alone or in conjunction with web beacons or other tracking technologies to collect information about you when you use our Website. The information they collect may be associated with your personal information or they may collect information, including personal information, about your online activities over time and across different websites and other online services. They may use this information to provide you with interest-based (behavioral) advertising or other targeted content.  
**(B)** We do not control these third parties’ tracking technologies or how they may be used. If you have any questions about an advertisement or other targeted content, you should contact the responsible provider directly.  
**(C)** Some of these third-party advertising companies may be advertising networks that are members of the Network Advertising Initiative, which offers a single location to opt out of ad targeting from member companies (www.networkadvertising.org). Opting out will not decrease the number of advertisements you see.  
**V. How We Use Your Information.**  
**(A)** We use information that we collect about you or that you provide to us, including any personal information:  
(i) To present our Website and its contents to you;  
(ii) To provide you with information, products, or services that you request from us;  
(iii) To fulfill any other purpose for which you provide it;  
(iv) To provide you with notices about the newsletter, including expiration and renewal notices;  
(v) To carry out our obligations and enforce our rights arising from any contracts entered into between you and us, including for billing and collection;  
(vi) To perform research and analysis about your use of, or interest in, our or others’ products, services, or content;  
(vii) To communicate with you via email or mobile devices about products, venues, or services that may be of interest to you either from us or other third parties;  
(viii) To develop, display, and track content and advertising tailored to your interests on the Website;  
(ix) To provide or analyze Website analytics;  
(x) To verify your eligibility and deliver prizes in connection with any contests and sweepstakes;  
(xi) To notify you about changes to our Website or any products or services we offer or provide though it;  
(xii) In any other way we may describe when you provide the information;  
(xiii) For any other purpose with your consent; or  
(xiv) We may use the information we have collected from you to enable us to display advertisements to our advertisers’ target audiences. Even though we do not disclose your personal information for these purposes without your consent, if you click on or otherwise interact with an advertisement, the advertiser may assume that you meet its target criteria.  
**(B)** In all circumstances listed in (A) above, we may perform these functions directly or use a third-party vendor to perform these functions on our behalf who will be obligated to use your personal information only to perform services for us. Also, if you access our Website from a third party social platform, such as Facebook, we may share non-personal information with that platform to the extent permitted by your agreement with it and its privacy settings. Please note that this Privacy Policy does not create rights enforceable by third parties or require disclosure of any personal information relating to users of the Website.  
**(C)** If you are a job applicant or service provider to the Company, and your personal information is submitted through the Website when applying for a position or job with the Company, the information will be used solely to consider and act upon your application materials. We may retain your personal information, but only to consider your application for current or future available positions or jobs. This information, which may include your name and contact information, prior education and experience, and other information you provide to us, may be shared with third-party service providers retained by us to collect, maintain, and analyze candidate submissions for job postings.  
**(D)** If you contact our support team through the Website, we will receive your email address, and may track your IP address as well as the information you send to us to help resolve your query. We will keep records of our communications with you, including any complaints or reports that we receive from you about other users (and from other users about you). We will not provide you information about users who report you.  
**VI. Disclosure of Your Information.**  
**(A)** We may disclose aggregated information about our users, and information that does not identify any individual, without restriction. We may disclose personal information that we collect or you provide as described in this Privacy Policy:  
(i) To our subsidiaries and affiliates;  
(ii) To contractors, service providers, and other third parties we use to support our business and who are bound by contractual obligations to keep personal information confidential and use it only for the purposes for which we disclose it to them;  
(iii) To a buyer or other successor in the event of a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution, or other sale or transfer of some or all of the Company’s assets, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation, or similar proceeding, in which personal information held by the Company about Website users is among the assets transferred;  
(iv) To fulfill the purpose for which you provide it;  
(v) For any other purpose disclosed by us when you provide the information; or  
(vi) With your consent.  
**(B)** We may also disclose your personal information:  
(i) To comply with any court order, law, or legal process, including to respond to any government or regulatory request;  
(ii) To enforce or apply our Terms of Use and other agreements; or  
(iii) If we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property, or safety of the Company, Website users, or others.  
**VII. Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information.**  
We strive to provide you with choices regarding the personal information you provide to us. We have created mechanisms to provide you with the following control over your information:  
**(A)** Tracking Technologies and Advertising. You can set your browser to refuse all or some browser cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. To learn how you can manage your Flash cookie settings, visit the Flash player settings page on Adobe’s website. If you disable or refuse cookies, please note that some parts of this site may then be inaccessible or not function properly.  
**(B)** Targeted Advertising. If you do not want us to use information that we collect or that you provide to us to deliver advertisements per our advertisers’ target-audience preferences, you can opt out by sending us an email stating your request to contact@libertywritersnews.com.  
**(C)** Do Not Track Disclosure. Do Not Track (“DNT”) is a privacy preference that users can set in their web browsers. DNT is a way for users to inform websites and services that they do not want certain information about their webpage visits collected over time and across websites or online services. However, because of the uncertainty of DNT in the internet industry, and the various factors and players conforming compliance, we may not recognize nor respond to DNT signals.  
**VIII. Accessing and Correcting Your Information.**  
If you choose to close your account or terminate your relationship with the Services, including by unsubscribing from the newsletter, we will retain certain information associated with your account for analytical purposes and recordkeeping integrity, as well as to prevent fraud, enforce our Terms of Use, take actions we deem necessary to protect the integrity of our Services or our users, or take other actions otherwise permitted by law. In addition, if certain information has already been provided to third parties as described in this Privacy Policy above, retention of that information will be subject to those companies’ policies, typically found on their websites.  
**IX. Deactivation; Termination of Your Account.**  
**(A)** When your account is deactivated or terminated, for any or no reason as may be determined by the Terms of Use, we take reasonable efforts to make sure it is no longer viewable on the Website. We are not responsible for any information, pictures, comments, or other content that is deleted from our systems resulting from the deactivation of your account.  
**(B)** To prevent abuse of the Website by a user following termination or deletion of an account, we shall retain such information as we deem in our sole discretion may be necessary to ensure that the user does not open a new account or profile in violation of our Terms of Use or other restrictions, and to ensure compliance with all laws and regulations.  
**(C)** After you remove information from your profile, if you created one, or delete your account, copies of that information may still be viewable or accessed to the extent such information has been previously shared with others, or copied or stored by other users or to the extent such information has been shared with search engines. We cannot control this, nor do we accept any liability for this. If you have given third party applications or websites access to your personal information, they may retain such information to the extent permitted subject to their respective terms of service or privacy policies. Removed and deleted information may persist in backup copies owned by the Company for up to 30 days to enable restoration or reactivation subject to successful appeal to Company, but will not be available to other users in the meantime.  
**X. Your California Privacy Rights.**  
California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits users of our Website that are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an email to contact@libertywritersnews.com.  
**XI. Data Security.**  
We have implemented measures designed to secure your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration, and disclosure. The safety and security of your information also depends on you. Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information transmitted to our Website. Any transmission of personal information is at your own risk. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Website.  
**XII. Communicating with You.**  
We may provide you with emails, alerts and other messages related to the Website, such as enhancements, offers, products, events and other promotions. With respect to other types of messaging or communications, such as emails, you can unsubscribe or opt out by either following the specific instructions included in such communications, or by emailing us with your request at contact@libertywritersnews.com.  
**XIII. Changes to Our Privacy Policy.**  
It is our policy to post any changes we make to our Privacy Policy to this subdomain page. If we make material changes to how we treat our users’ personal information, we will notify you by email to the email address you may have provided us, or through a notice on the Website. The date this Privacy Policy was last revised is identified at the top of the page. You are responsible for ensuring we have an up-to-date, active and deliverable email address for you, and for periodically visiting our Website and this Privacy Policy to check for any changes.  
XIV. Contact Information.  
To ask questions or comment about this Privacy Policy and our privacy practices, contact us at contact@libertywritersnews.com.
